webgistix.com 2012-10-30

# Drop Ship Fulfillment: ecommerce Fulfillment Services by Webgistix

PRIVACY

**Web Site Privacy Statement**

_Last Updated December 2010_

**Your Privacy is Important to Us**

Webgistix Corporation ("Webgistix") has created this Privacy Statement to inform you of the information collection practices for this Web site, www.Webgistix.com ("Web Site"), including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, you should first contact Webgistix by sending an email to [privacy@webgistix.com](mailto:privacy@webgistix.com) or by regular mail to the attention of Privacy Manager, Webgistix Corporation, 880 Wigwam Parkway #120, Henderson NV 89014. If you are emailing or mailing Webgisitix to lodge a complaint, you must include the following information: the name of company, the alleged privacy violation, your contact information, and whether you would like the particulars of your complaint shared with the company. 

Webgistix complies with the EU Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. 

**Personally Identifiable Information that We Collect**   
In general, you can visit this Web Site without identifying yourself or revealing any personally identifiable information. There are times, however, that you may choose to give us personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address and other information about yourself. For example, if you would like to receive an assessment and proposal from Webgistix, you will need to provide us information such as your name, address, telephone and/or fax number. If you sign up for e-mail updates, you will need to provide us with your e-mail address. If you choose to unsubscribe from emails, please click unsubscribe in the applicable email message. In response to employment opportunities at Webgistix, you may submit your resume through this Web Site. We also provide you with the opportunity to e-mail us questions or comments about this Web Site and our Company. 

We post testimonials on this Web Site which may contain personally identifiable information. Prior to posting each testimonial, we obtain the company representative's consent to post their name along with their testimonial. 

If you use a bulletin board, chat room, blog or forum on this Web Site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. 

**Our Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information**   
We only use the personally identifiable information that you provide through this Web Site to help us improve our services to you, to provide you with the information you have requested, to respond to your questions or resume submission, and for other internal purposes. Any non-personally identifiable material, information, suggestions, ideas, concepts, know-how, techniques, questions, comments or other communication you transmit or post to this Web Site in any manner is and will be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary ("User Communications"). Webgistix, each of our affiliates and/or their designees may use any or all User Communications for any purpose whatsoever, including, without limitation, reproduction, transmission, disclosure, publication, broadcast, development, manufacturing and/or marketing in any manner whatsoever for any or all commercial or non-commercial purposes. Webgistix may, but is not obligated to, monitor or review any information you provide through this Web Site. Webgistix shall have no obligations to use, return, review, or respond to any requests, information, questions, material, comments, submissions or other communications through this Web Site. You are prohibited from posting or transmitting to or from this Web Site any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, offensive, or pornographic material, or material that would violate any law. Webgistix will have no liability related to the content of any such communications, whether or not arising under the laws of copyright, libel, privacy, obscenity, or otherwise. 

**Access to Your Personally Identifiable Information**   
If you would like to access personally identifiable information that you have provided through this Web Site to correct or request deletion, please contact us as described below. We will respond to your request within 30 days. 

**Third Party Access to Your Personally Identifiable Information**   
Webgistix will not sell, rent, or lease to others any personally identifiable information that you provide through this Web Site. Unless we have your permission, we will only share the personally identifiable information you provide through this Web Site with other Webgistix entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described in this Privacy Statement. All Webgistix entities and/or business partners having access to your personally identifiable information are subject to this Privacy Statement with respect to the use of your personally identifiable information. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required or permitted by law, or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order, a law enforcement request, or other legal process served on this Web Site. 

We use third parties to provide job search services on this Web Site. When you sign up for these services, we will share your personally identifiable information as necessary for the applicable third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

**Information Security and Quality**   
We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational measures to help us keep your information secure, accurate, current, and complete. We will make a sincere effort to respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccuracies in your personally identifiable information. To correct inaccuracies or to delete the personally identifiable information we have about you, please return the message containing the inaccuracies to the sender with details of the correction requested, or send an email to [privacy@webgistix.com](mailto:privacy@webgistix.com), or send your request by regular mail to the attention of Privacy Manager, Webgistix Corporation, 880 Wigwam Parkway #120, Henderson NV 89014. We will respond to your request within 30 days. 

**Technologies on this Web Site**   
As is true of most Web Sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer this Web Site, to track users' movements around this Web Site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. We use a third-party tracking service that uses tracking technologies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to this Web Site in the aggregate. 

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this Web Site. We do link the information we store in cookies to your personally identifiable information you submit while on this Web Site. 

This Web Site includes "widgets", which are interactive mini-programs that provide specific services from another company. For example, one of the widgets on this Web Site redirects you to a web-based feed reader to subscribe to our blog. Information collected by this widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it. 

**Links to Other Web Sites**   
From time to time, this Web Site may contain links to other Web sites. If you use these links, you will leave this Web Site. The privacy policies of such other Web sites govern the information collection and dissemination practices occurring on such Web sites. Neither Webgistix nor its affiliates is responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Questions Concerning this Privacy Statement**   
Questions regarding this Privacy Statement should be directed to Webgistix by e-mail to [privacy@webgistix.com](mailto:privacy@webgistix.com) or by regular mail to the attention of Privacy Manager. Webgistix Corporation, 880 Wigwam Parkway #120, Henderson NV 89014. 

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**   
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Statement, we will notify you by means of a notice on our home page.
